Everyone loved him. Few knew him.
Belushi is a documentary film directed by R. J. Cutler.
Using previously unheard audiotapes recorded shortly
after John Belushi’s death, director R.J.
Cutler’s documentary feature examines the too-short life of the once-in-a-generation
talent who captured the hearts and funny bones of devoted audiences.
Self (archive footage), played by John Belushi.
Self (archive footage), played by Judith Belushi-Pisano.
Self (archive footage), played by Harold Ramis.
Self (archive footage), played by Dan Aykroyd.
Self (archive footage), played by Chevy Chase.
Self (archive footage), played by John Landis.
Belushi is a 2020 American documentary film about John
Belushi, a comedian, actor, and singer.
The film is directed, written, and produced by R.
Cutler, based on interviews conducted for the book
Belushi: A Biography by Tanner Colby.
The film explores themes of comedian, drugs, manic depression.
The tone is lighthearted.